New York State Federation of Home Bureaus Records.
New York State Federation of Home Bureaus Records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
New York State Federation of Home Bureaus records, 1915-1991.
23-17-853
New York State College of Home Economics.
12 cubic feet.
Correspondence, Manuscripts, Photographs, Printed Materials, Reports
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
New York State Federation of Home Bureaus records including minutes, programs, reports, clippings, and photos.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
New York State Federation of Home Bureaus records including minutes, programs, reports, clippings, and photos; Associated Countrywomen of the World files with correspondence and mimeographed items about its conferences; New York State Council of Rural Women file including correspondence and minutes; Extension files concerning organization, purpose, and administration; Home Demonstration work files; Older Rural Youth files; Conference files; Farm and Home Week Files; and Nutrition Institute and Nutrition Committee files including correspondence, reports, programs, lists, photos, and other items, many pertaining to wartime nutrition. Also, press releases, with interfiled correspondence and program material; annual reports 1918-1977, 1958 membership study, and a copy of Lucinda Noble's 1958 master's thesis entitled A Study of Training Needs of Home Demonstration Agents in New York.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State College of Home Economics.; Associated Country Women of the World.; Cornell University.; New York State College of Agriculture.Extension Service.; New York State Council of Rural Women.; New York State Federation of Home Bureaus.; New York State Nutrition Committee.
Subjects:
Home economics extension work--New York (State); Home economics extension workers--New York (State); Nutrition extension work--New York (State); Home demonstration work--New York (State); Home economics--Study and teaching.; Women in agriculture.; Women--Societies and clubs.; 4-H clubs--New York (State)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Correspondence, memos dealing with extension work in Home Ec. that led to the establishment of the Home Bureau, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Reports by agents to the Farm Bureau - women agents. Letters and memo concerning the use of women agents, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Minutes of meetings of Home Economic Conferences, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Report of Home Demonstration work, 1917-07-01-1918-04 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Home demonstation circulars, correspondence, 1918-02-1918-09 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Reports on the growth of Home Bureaus in New York State and Home Economics Extension, 1917-1918 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Organization charts for College of Agriculture and Department of Home Economics, 1918-10-01-1918-12-23 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Correspondence between dept. members, official statement of Central Office Policies, material for Farm House Survey, 1919-01-20-1919-08-12 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Correspondence and circulars, 1919-09-02-1919-12-12 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Strengthening organization, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- History of Smith-Lever Act (includes history of Farm and Home Bureau), 1921-04 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Annual report to Dean Mann, 1921-07-01 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, bulletins, and organization charts, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, bulletins, and organization charts, 1923-01-21-1926-07 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Notes on the development of the Home Bureau Informational Program Report, 1927-1946 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Mimeographed material - no correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Mimeographed material including organization chart reflecting the evaluation of Farm Bureau Extension Service Relations, 1949-1951 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- History of Extension and Farm Bureau, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Reports of background material for realignment, new relationship between College and Federation, 1954-01-06-1954-05-19 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Reports of difficulties encountered in making the transition, 1954-06-07-1954-12-06 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Reports of difficulties encountered in making the transition, 1955-03-03-1955-06-06 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Change becomes official Jan. 1, 1956, 1955-07-13-1957-12-09 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Lists of officers and committees in the Home Bureau, 1919-1954 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Minutes of central district and county meetings, 1928-1939 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Minutes of eastern district and county meetings, 1928-1938 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Minutes of northern district and county meetings, 1928-1935 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Minutes of western district and county meetings, 1926-1947 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- History of the American Farm Breau Federation by Director L.R. Simons, 1939-12-13 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Home Bureau membership, 1919-1942 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Undated material, much of which deals with the organization and goals of the Farm Bureau in its early days (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Minutes, programs, and notes of the organizational meetings of the New York State Federation of Home Bureaus, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Mimeographed copies of the Board of Directors meetings, 1945-1953 (Box 1, Folder 32-35)
- Mimeographed programs of Citizen Leader Training Schools, 1947-1953 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Constitution and by-laws of the Home Bureau; some constitutions of communities, counties, and districts (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Annual meeting minutes, 1920-1935 (Box 1, Folder 39-54)
- Annual meeting minutes, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 55-56)
- Annual meeting minutes, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Lists of delegates who visited Cornell in June 1936, report on Home Dem. exhibit at the Third Triennial Conference at Work, copy of a talk given by Mrs. Alfred Watt- President of the Associated Country Women of the World, 1936-1939 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Minutes of the 1941 regional conference of the ACWW and the 1945 executive committee, its amended constitution of 1947, 1948 report entitled "The World Situation from a Woman's Point of View", 1941-1948 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Mimeographed and printed news items, lists of personnel and officers, 1949-1952 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Matters concerning accomodations for the delegates at the 7th Triennial Conference in Toronto, Canada, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Information on the Ceylon conference in 1956, 1959 handbook, 1954-1959 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Photographs from the 1936 ACWW meeting and 1953 barbecue (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Photograph of Anne Phillips Duncan and child, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Plays and Pageants: Folder I - Three plays, 1921-1923 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Plays and Pageants: Folder II - Two plays and a movie scenario, 1924-27 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Plays, pageants, and poems (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Programs of the Home Bureau's annual meetings, 1919-1939 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Programs of the Home Bureau's annual meetings, 1940-1957 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Printed material (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Minutes of meetings of the Public Relations Committee (Federation and Home Demonstration Agents), 1953-1958 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Recommendations and programs, 1932-1943 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Formal resignations from the Federation, 1955-07-11-1956-01-16 (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
- Scholarship winners, 1928-1956 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Songs (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Study of women enrolled in Home Dem. work, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Meeting minutes of New York State Council of Rural Women, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Meeting minutes of New York State Council of Rural Women, 1936-1938 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Meeting minutes of New York State Council of Rural Women, 1939-1941 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Meeting minutes of New York State Council of Rural Women, leaflets, address by Grove B. Hill and Secretary of Agriculture Emily Newell Blair, 1942-1943 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Meeting minutes of New York State Council of Rural Women, 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Meeting minutes of New York State Council of Rural Women, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Meeting minutes of New York State Council of Rural Women, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Meeting minutes of New York State Council of Rural Women, 1949-1950 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Meeting minutes of New York State Council of Rural Women, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Meeting minutes of New York State Council of Rural Women, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Meeting minutes of New York State Council of Rural Women, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Meeting minutes of New York State Council of Rural Women, 1954-59 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Various items (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Report on expansion of extension work, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Information on Food Marketing Service, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Report on the Fourth Annual Conference of Junior Extension leaders, 1921-1923 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Various items, some of the History of Cornell University by R.G. Smith (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Administrative material, 1916-1928 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Secretary's manual (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Extension studies (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Extension - Teaching Evaluation (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Aids for publicizing 4-H Club Achievement Week, fact sheet for 1949, 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Programs of 4-H Club Congress, transcriptions of radio interview, oth, 1947-1949 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Fourteenth Annual Meeting of 4-H Club Federation, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Programs, 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Club prospects, 1942,1947 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- By-laws of the 4-H Club Foundation, Inc. (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Press release of the 4-H Club Extension Federation meetings, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Program for Training School for Summer Assistants in 4-H Club work, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Program for Economics of the Household Training School, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Programs and report for Leadership Training School in Child Development and Family Relations, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Program for Ext. Sec. Workshop, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Programs for Ext. Workers Schedule, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Program and script of Home Dem. Agents' conference, 1945-1949 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Program, brief report on material covered, and press releases for Home Dem. Agents subject matter Training School, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Home Dem. reports, 1926-1947 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Program for Home Ec. Extension Canning-Training School, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Announcements of Jefferson County Dairyland Festival, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Minutes of the Board of Directors, 1945,1949 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- NYS Home Bureau Memos, 1940s-1950s (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Farm and Home Bureau Records, 1950s (Box 15, Folder 3)
- NYS Federation of the Home Bureaus - Organizational charts, 1950s (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Minutes of the Board of Directors, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, Memoranda Concerning Home Bureau and State Federations, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, Memoranda Concerning Home Bureau Realignment, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Minutes of the Board Meetings and Memos, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- NYS Federation of Home Bureau Memos, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, Memoranda Concerning Home Bureau Federation, Realignment of Home Demonstrators, 1955-01-1955-03 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Home Bureau Federation Programs from different districts, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Associated County Women of the World
  - Letters of National Home Dem. Agents Association, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Fact sheets, press releases, programs for National Home Dem. Week, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Fact sheets, press releases, programs for National Home Dem. Week, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Fact sheets, press releases, programs for National Home Dem. Week, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Fact sheets, press releases, programs for National Home Dem. Week, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Items on Older Rural Youth, 1945-1949 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Items on Older Rural Youth Conference-Watkins Glen, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Items on County Rural Policy Committees, 1937-1944 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Items on New York State Department of Health, 1937-1944 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Items on New York State Food Commission, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - USDA Division of Extension Info- notes on Famine Emergency Campaign, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Names and titles of USDA Extension Service, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Booklet for Federal Housing Administration (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Prod. & Marketing Administration information, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Conferences at Cornell
  - American Association of Agricultural College Editors - Annual Conference, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - American College Public Relations Association District I - Annual Meeting, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - College Club Workshop, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Cornell School for Missionaties, 1941-1949 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Dedication of Savage Hall, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Eighteenth Anniversary, Cornell University, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Food Preservation Conference, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Future Homemakers of America - Annual Meeting, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Home Economics Teachers Conference, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Household Equipment Conference, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Institute for Parent-Teacher Leaders, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - New York State Homemaking Teachers' Conference - press releases, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - New York State Nutrition Committee - program and press releases, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - New York State Nutrition Conference - correspondence, speeches, press releases, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - New York State Nutrition Institute - press releases, programs, 1946-1948 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Speakers Institute of Home and Farm Safety - press releases, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Tuberculosis and Public Health Committee - programs, press releases, talks, 1948-1948 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Veterans' Wives Charm School - program, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Visual Aids Workshop - attendance and program, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Women in Radio - program, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Conferences Out-Of-Town
  - American Association of Agricultural College Editors - National Meeting, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - American Association of Agricultural College Editors - Annual Meeting, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - American Association of Agricultural Editors - Annual Meeting, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - American Association of Agricultural Editors - Northeastern Meeting, 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Association of Women Broadcasters - Annual Meeting - programs, correspondence, talks, attendance, press releases, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Association of Women Broadcasters - Annual Meeting - talks, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Association of Women Broadcasters- District Meeting - program and notes, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Association of Women Broadcasters - District Meeting - program and notes, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Association of Women Broadcasters - District Meeting - program, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Family Life Conference - Regional - program, resume, press releases, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - New York State Conference on the Use of Radio in Home and Farm Safety Education - program and magazine article, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Nutrition Comittee Leadership Lists, 1940-1945 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Farm and Home Week
  - Farm and Home Week Exhibit, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Farm and Home Week Exhibit, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Farm and Home Week - Plans, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Farm and Home Week - Plans, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Farm and Home Week - Plans, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Farm and Home Week - Publicity, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Farm and Home Week - Publicity, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Farm and Home Week - Talks, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Farm and Home Week - Talks, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Farm and Home Train, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Organizations
  - The American College Public Relations Association, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - American Fat Salvage Committee, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - American Home Economics Association - Bulletin, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Cornell Press - Radio Dinner, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Future Homemakers of America, 1946-47 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Home Department Handbook - Dairymen's League, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - House Organs - Lists, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - National Concil of Farmer Cooperatives - Information Bulletin (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - National Dairy Council - Publications, 1939-1945 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - National Education Association - Department of Higher Education - College and University Bulletin, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - National Safety Council - Farm Safety Announcements, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - National Secretaries Association - Ithaca Chapter - Programs, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Women's Colleges in New York State - Lists (Box 3, Folder 55)
- College of Agriculture
  - College of Agriculture - Department of Extension Teaching and Information, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - College of Agriculture - Department of Extension Teaching and Information, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - College of Agriculture - Department of Extension Teaching and Information, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - College of Agriculture - Department of Extension Teaching and Information, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - College of Agriculture - Department of Extension Teaching and Information, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - College of Agriculture - Department of Extension Teaching and Information - Mailing Room, 1946-1949 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- College of Home Economics
  - College of Home Economics and Administration, 1944-1946 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - College of Home Economics and Administration, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - College of Home Economics and Administration, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - College of Home Economics and Administration, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - College of Home Economics - Food Marketing Service, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - College of Home Economics - General, 1944-1949 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - College of Home Economics - Personnel Office, 1946-1949 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - College of Home Economics - Radio, 1945-1949 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - College of Home Economics - Photographic Science, 1947-1949 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - College of Home Economics - Visual Aids, 1946-1949 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- Miscellaneous
  - Child Development and Family Relationships, 1942-1950 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - College of Arts and Sciences - General, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Department of Economics of the Household and Household Management, 1943-1949 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Department of Rural Sociology, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Extension Secretary, 1946-1949 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Extension Studies, 1947-1949 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Food and Nutrition Department, 1944-1949 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - 4-H Club Office, 1943-1949 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Home Economics Education Department, 1946-1949 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Home Economics Extension Agents, 1943-1949 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Hotel Administration, 1946-1949 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Housing and Design Department, 1942-1949 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Industrial and Labor Relations, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Institutional Management, 1944-1949 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - New York Hospital of Nursing, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Rural Housing, 1946-1949 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Textiles and Clothing Department, 1946-1949 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - University Library, 1947-1949 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - University Press, 1946-1948 (Box 3, Folder 90)
- New York State Nutrition Committees - 1940s - Minutes, Memos, Flyers, Reports, Photographs
  - Albany (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Allegany (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Broome (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Cattaraugus (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Cayuga (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Chautauqua (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Chemung (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Chemung (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Chenango (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Clinton (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Columbia (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Cortland (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Delaware (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Dutchess (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Erie (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Erie (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Erie (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Erie Co. nutrition exhibits (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Essex (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Franklin (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Fulton (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Genesee (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Greene (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Hamilton (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Herkimer (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Jefferson (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Lewis (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Livingston (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Madison (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Monroe (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Monroe (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Monroe (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Montgomery (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Nassau (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - NYC (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - NYC (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - NYC (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Niagara (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Oneida (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Oneida (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Oneida (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Oneida (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Onondaga (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Onondaga (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Ontario (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Orange (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Orange (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Orleans (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Oswego (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Otsego (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Otsego (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Putnam (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Rensselaer (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Rockland (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - St. Lawrence (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - St. Lawrence (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Saratoga (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Schenectady (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Schoharie (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Schuyler (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Seneca (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Steuben (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Suffolk (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Sullivan (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Tioga (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Tompkins (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Tompkins (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Tompkins (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Ulster (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Warren (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Washington (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Wayne (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Westchester (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Westchester (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Westchester (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Wyoming (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Yates (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - New York State Nutrition Conference, 1940 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Committee: History and Development (Box 5)
  - Foods and Nutrition Conference, 1937 (Box 5)
  - New York State Nutrition Conference, 1939 (Box 5)
  - New York State Nutrition Conference, 1939 (Box 5)
  - New York State Nutrition Conference, 1940 (Box 5)
  - New York State Nutrition Conference, 1940 (Box 5)
  - New York State Nutrition Conference, 1940 (Box 5)
  - New York State Nutrition Conference, 1941 (Box 5)
  - New York State Nutrition Conference, 1942 (Box 5)
  - Food Preservation Conference, 1944 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Conference, 1945 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Institute, 1946 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Institute, 1947 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Institute, 1948 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Institute, 1949 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Institute, 1949 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Institute, 1950 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Institute, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Committee Personnel, 1940-1941 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Committee Personnel, 1940-1941 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Committee Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Committee Correspondence, 1942-1943 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Committee Correspondence, 1944-1946 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Committee Correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Committee Correspondence, 1949-1951 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Committee Civil Defense, 1951 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Committee Lesson Seires, 1941 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Committee Minutes, 1940-1941 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Committee Minutes, 1942 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Committee Minutes, 1943-1944 (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous, 1940-1945 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Committee Minutes, 1945-1946 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Committee Minutes, 1947-1948 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Committee Minutes, 1949-1951 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Committee Library Committee, 1941 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Committeee Reports to Lieut. Gov. Poletti, 1941-1942 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Forthnight, 1941 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Fortnight, 1941 (Box 5)
  - Nutrition Fortnight, 1941 (Box 5)